<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscs on The Radnor Arms</title>
    <link>radnorarms.github.io/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscs on The Radnor Arms</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="radnorarms.github.io/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Opening Times</title>
      <link>radnorarms.github.io/misc/opening-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>radnorarms.github.io/misc/opening-times/</guid>
      <description>Temporary Restricted Opening Hours from August 21st Bar Monday Closed Tuesday Closed Wednesday 5:30 - 10:00pm Thursday 5:30 - 10:00pm Friday 12:00 - 2:00pm 5:30 - 10:30pm Saturday 12:00 - 2:30pm 5:30 - 10:30pm Sunday Closed The above hours are temporary while Andrew recuperates from a long a-waited shoulder operation. We will endeavour to get back to normal as soon as we can.
The hours may be subject to short notice change, so it is advisable to call prior to visiting us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>radnorarms.github.io/misc/tier-trade-restrictons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>radnorarms.github.io/misc/tier-trade-restrictons/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 Tier Restrictions Current COVID-19 Tier hospitality restrictions are putting particular pressure on our little village pub due to its limited availability of dining tables.
In an attempt to attain viable trade, balanced with customer safety regulations, we have been forced to implement the following provisional dining-in terms:
Booking It is strongly advised that you pre-books tables, especially on Friday evening, Saturday evening and the Sunday Lunch services.
Booking terms &amp;amp; conditions will be explained at the time of booking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>radnorarms.github.io/misc/xmas-tier-trade-restrictons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>radnorarms.github.io/misc/xmas-tier-trade-restrictons/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 Tier Restrictions Christmas Day and New Years Eve Current COVID-19 Tier hospitality restrictions are putting particular pressure on our little village pub due to its limited availability of dining tables.
In an attempt to attain viable trade, balanced with customer safety regulations, we have been forced to implement the following provisional dining-in terms:
Sittings From 5.00pm must be booked for either food or drinks; tables are bookable in two-hour slots with the main food services operating two sittings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
